[
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ر ا ز ي ك ا ❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ر و ز و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛و ك ز ي ن و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ي ن ا م ن ا❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا م ي ر ن❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "مارين"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛و م ر ا ك ا ي ش❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "شيكامارو"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا ب د ي❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "دابي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛غ ي ش ر ا ك ا ي❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "شيغاراكي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا م ن ي❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ت ا ي ن ه ا❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا ت ب ا ف و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "فوتابا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ي ن ي ل ي ل❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نيليل"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا ك ن و ن❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "كونان"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ب ي س ر❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "سيبر"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ل ي و ي س و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا ي م ي❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛و ش ر ا ي ا و م  ر ت و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "اوروتشيمارو"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ك و س ن ا و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "سوكونا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ز ي ا ن❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ايزن"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ن ا س و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "سونا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ك م ي و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ميكو"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ف ي ل ي ا❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ف ل ي و❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ك ا م س ي ا❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛و ر ز ث❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ثورز"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ش ا ي د ل ا❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "اشيلاد"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ا ن ب و ا ر❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛و م ن❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "مون"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ر ك ي ا ر❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "كيرا"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ي ر ن❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "رين"
    },
{
        "question": "‗رتب ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛ي ا س❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ساي"
    }
  

]